<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Longsley]]></title>
  <link href="http://longsley.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://longsley.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-02-02T21:25:25-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://longsley.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Longsley]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brand New]]></title>
    <link href="http://longsley.github.io/blog/brand-new/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-02T20:26:59-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://longsley.github.io/blog/brand-new</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello. My name is Longsley and I am brand new. I am hoping to build from scratch a network of like-minded individuals who share my passion for the use of technology to improve the world. I believe war and inequality can be made obsolete. I hope to explore these and other topics through blogging and other online social activities. I also aim to do this completely anonymously.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>My reasons for maintaining my anonymity are varied and complex and will be explored in future blog posts. The short explanation is that I can truly speak my mind only if I don&rsquo;t have to worry about how my views and words will affect the ones I love.</p>

<p>To secure my anonymity, I have endeavored to only connect to services related to Longsley via <a href="http://torproject.org">Tor</a>. I have settled for a Yandex email address as the major webmail providers require phone numbers these days. My Twitter account is currently <a href="https://support.twitter.com/articles/15790">suspended</a> (likely due to connecting through Tor and signing up with a Yandex email address&hellip;), but I have filed an appeal and have every expectation that it will be reinstated. I have also kept completely silent about this project to anyone with whom I have a personal connection.</p>

<p>My anonymity is not perfect. The Tor network could be compromised. My hardware or software could be backdoored. I could eventually make a mistake and access Longsley-related services in an insecure manner. The important thing is that I&rsquo;ve taken the precautions I am willing to take and I am now confident enough to go to work.</p>

<h3>I need your help</h3>

<p>As Longsley, I have no contacts. I know no one. I have words and ideas and passion and ambition and brains and guts, but I have no influence. I can publish this post and literally no one will see it.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
